<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Friday Update on SAFA</title>
    <link>https://studentactivistsforamerica.github.io/categories/friday-update/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Friday Update on SAFA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Blog by SAFA</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://studentactivistsforamerica.github.io/categories/friday-update/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday Update 1/27/17</title>
      <link>https://studentactivistsforamerica.github.io/2017/01/friday-update-1/27/17/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://studentactivistsforamerica.github.io/2017/01/friday-update-1/27/17/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Happy Friday SAFA Volunteers! Every Friday we will be releasing an update summing up the week, telling you our plans for the future, and detailing what you can do over the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;recap-of-the-week&#34;&gt;Recap of the Week&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a lot to go over this week, as we started it all on Tuesday. We organized SAFA and determined our debut event: the bake sale for Planned Parenthood. You can look at the previous couple of posts to see the details of that, but to summarize, we chose a date (2/9/17 and 2/10/17), locations (Nueva and Hillsdale Mall), created sign up sheets, and have started to flesh out the event even more. I (Aidan) talked to the Planned Parenthood leadership office to understand what the best way we can help them is. They gave us a few ideas, including: fundraising, volunteering at a local charter, educating people, and spreading awareness for their lack of funding. We also started drafting our manifesto, in hopes that it will shed some light on our vision and goals for SAFA. In general, we developed our organization and our first ever event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;plans-for-the-future&#34;&gt;Plans for the Future&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our largest, and the one that will happen in the close future, plan is the bake sale. As I said before, if you want details, look at our previous messages and subsequent messages. However, here, I will talk about the general ideal picture of what we want to happen. Although we have not formed an actual goal, I think we want to raise upwards of $200. In addition to that, we want a good number of volunteers to bake, hopefully making a lot of treats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the farther future, we hope to create a website to inform activists, like you, of our activities. We also want to expand our presence on social media and start recruiting more people for this organization. Establishing a formal leadership is also on our to-do along. Finally, we are discussing whether to file for incorporation as a nonprofit (501c4) so we can have our own bank account and other benefits. We will be working on these goals once we complete the bake sale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-you-can-do-over-the-weekend&#34;&gt;What you can do over the Weekend&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the most important things you can do is sign up to bring treats. You can, and should, sign up right now to help us. If you can&amp;rsquo;t bring food, we strongly encourage you to get people who can bring food to bring food. There are other ways to help and we will publish a list of what we need volunteers to do (beside baking food) soon, so watch out for that in the near future. If you can&amp;rsquo;t do anything, just try to spread information about us and get others to help!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We did a lot this week, like founding this organization. We still have a lot to do in the future, such as establishing a leadership and running our first event, a bake sale. Once again, keep looking at this channel and keep volunteering! Happy friday and have a good weekend!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The SAFA Leadership&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>