<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SAFA</title>
    <link>https://studentactivistsforamerica.github.io/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on SAFA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Blog by SAFA</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 22:43:02 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://studentactivistsforamerica.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>NoBanNoWall SF Protest</title>
      <link>https://studentactivistsforamerica.github.io/2017/01/nobannowall-sf-protest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 22:43:02 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://studentactivistsforamerica.github.io/2017/01/nobannowall-sf-protest/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Hello SAFA! We hope you&amp;rsquo;re having a good day and are staying updated with he news and active about what&amp;rsquo;s happening. Just to plug it once again, we are still looking for bakers for the Planned Parenthood bake sale. But, to the point, we are letting you know about a new protests, protesting Trump&amp;rsquo;s immigration policies that he has enacted. Here are the details:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;where&#34;&gt;Where&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UN Plaza/Civic Center in San Francisco&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;when&#34;&gt;When&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday February 4th from 3pm-6pm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;what&#34;&gt;What&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/events/1860032590936254/&#34;&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/1860032590936254/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;where-we-will-meet&#34;&gt;Where we will meet&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In front of the Asian Art Museum at 3pm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;other&#34;&gt;Other&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will have 4-7 signs for you to use. But feel free to bring your own sign if you want to. Although we aren&amp;rsquo;t keeping track, it would be helpful if you could let us know if you are going or thinking about going.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks,
The SAFA Leadership&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Short Update</title>
      <link>https://studentactivistsforamerica.github.io/2017/01/a-short-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://studentactivistsforamerica.github.io/2017/01/a-short-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are now &lt;strong&gt;10 days&lt;/strong&gt; away from the bake sale and we still have lots to do. One of the most important ways we need you to help is by baking for us. Right now, we have 5 people who have signed up to bake. Let&amp;rsquo;s try to get that to 10 people. If you are thinking about baking, please sign up. If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about it but not sure if you can, write in a note telling us that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the sign up sheet, and remember, we can&amp;rsquo;t do this without you:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://goo.gl/forms/Szp7UV3SSbBCvUki1&#34;&gt;https://goo.gl/forms/Szp7UV3SSbBCvUki1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks,
The SAFA Leadership&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;P.S. a longer update is coming soon, either today or tomorrow&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday Update 1/27/17</title>
      <link>https://studentactivistsforamerica.github.io/2017/01/friday-update-1/27/17/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://studentactivistsforamerica.github.io/2017/01/friday-update-1/27/17/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Happy Friday SAFA Volunteers! Every Friday we will be releasing an update summing up the week, telling you our plans for the future, and detailing what you can do over the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;recap-of-the-week&#34;&gt;Recap of the Week&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a lot to go over this week, as we started it all on Tuesday. We organized SAFA and determined our debut event: the bake sale for Planned Parenthood. You can look at the previous couple of posts to see the details of that, but to summarize, we chose a date (2/9/17 and 2/10/17), locations (Nueva and Hillsdale Mall), created sign up sheets, and have started to flesh out the event even more. I (Aidan) talked to the Planned Parenthood leadership office to understand what the best way we can help them is. They gave us a few ideas, including: fundraising, volunteering at a local charter, educating people, and spreading awareness for their lack of funding. We also started drafting our manifesto, in hopes that it will shed some light on our vision and goals for SAFA. In general, we developed our organization and our first ever event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;plans-for-the-future&#34;&gt;Plans for the Future&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our largest, and the one that will happen in the close future, plan is the bake sale. As I said before, if you want details, look at our previous messages and subsequent messages. However, here, I will talk about the general ideal picture of what we want to happen. Although we have not formed an actual goal, I think we want to raise upwards of $200. In addition to that, we want a good number of volunteers to bake, hopefully making a lot of treats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the farther future, we hope to create a website to inform activists, like you, of our activities. We also want to expand our presence on social media and start recruiting more people for this organization. Establishing a formal leadership is also on our to-do along. Finally, we are discussing whether to file for incorporation as a nonprofit (501c4) so we can have our own bank account and other benefits. We will be working on these goals once we complete the bake sale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-you-can-do-over-the-weekend&#34;&gt;What you can do over the Weekend&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the most important things you can do is sign up to bring treats. You can, and should, sign up right now to help us. If you can&amp;rsquo;t bring food, we strongly encourage you to get people who can bring food to bring food. There are other ways to help and we will publish a list of what we need volunteers to do (beside baking food) soon, so watch out for that in the near future. If you can&amp;rsquo;t do anything, just try to spread information about us and get others to help!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We did a lot this week, like founding this organization. We still have a lot to do in the future, such as establishing a leadership and running our first event, a bake sale. Once again, keep looking at this channel and keep volunteering! Happy friday and have a good weekend!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The SAFA Leadership&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grab &#39;em by the Cookie Event</title>
      <link>https://studentactivistsforamerica.github.io/2017/01/grab-em-by-the-cookie-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://studentactivistsforamerica.github.io/2017/01/grab-em-by-the-cookie-event/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our first event is &amp;ldquo;Grab &amp;lsquo;em by the cookie&amp;rdquo;, a bake sale for Women&amp;rsquo;s Health, with the proceeds going to Planned Parenthood. As any even, we need lots of volunteers and help to accomplish this task. Even if you can&amp;rsquo;t volunteer, you can still ask someone else if they would like to help. We will be updating you all right here, on this channel, as more info about the bake sale as we get closer to the date. But without further ado, here is the info we have:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When:&lt;/strong&gt;
Thursday February 9th and Friday February 10th&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where:&lt;/strong&gt;
On 2/9/17, we will be holding the sale at the Nueva School Bay Meadows Campus. On 2/10/17, the sale will be held at the Hillsdale Mall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we Need:&lt;/strong&gt;
We need volunteers to make treats and other goods for the sale. Fill out the form to sign up to bring something: &lt;a href=&#34;https://goo.gl/forms/Szp7UV3SSbBCvUki1&#34;&gt;https://goo.gl/forms/Szp7UV3SSbBCvUki1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for volunteering for this event and we hope it will be amazing!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introductions</title>
      <link>https://studentactivistsforamerica.github.io/2017/01/introductions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://studentactivistsforamerica.github.io/2017/01/introductions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone! We are SAFA, a political activism organization for Bay Area students. We focus on real issues that are present in today&amp;rsquo;s America, such as women&amp;rsquo;s health, racial discrimination, health care, poverty, the environment, and many more. We then take these issues and work to fix them, by holding fundraisers and donation drives, volunteering, protesting, and spreading awareness, usually working on one issue per month. The difference between our mission and that of other activism organizations is that we intend to engage students primarily and foster engagement in one&amp;rsquo;s community regardless of the individual causes that they work with specifically. This blog is primarily meant to inform and notify volunteers about activities and events we are running, however, we will also be posting information about protests that you can participate in. As we are just starting, we need your help! So help us out by spreading awareness of this organization and getting others involved in our events. Once again, thanks for volunteering!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The SAFA Leadership&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>